A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, International Program in Health Care Policy (IHP), SG 3, Series 14 FA1475
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Program in Health Care Policy (IHP), 1925-2006; 14
  - Harkness Fellowships Administration, 3
    - 1999-2000 Harkness Fellows - Suggested Projects (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellowships - New Zealand - Applications - 01-001NZ - 01-019NZ (Box 132)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellowships - Australia - Applications - 01-001AUS - 01-008AUS (Box 133)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellowships - UK Applicants, 2000-2001 (Box 142)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellowships - New Zealand Applicants - Not Selected (Box 145)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellowships - Australia Applicants - Not Selected (Box 146)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellowships - Australia Applicants - Not Selected (Box 147)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellowships - New Zealand - Selection Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 147)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellowships - General Correspondence (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellowships - Contacts and Placements (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellowships - AHSR Project Database (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - 1999 Harkness Fellowships - Application Pack (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - 1999-2000 Applicants (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Harkness Fellows 2000-2001 Nominees - Applications Sent (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - 1999-2000 Application Pack (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - 1999 Harkness Fellows - General Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - 1999 Harkness Fellows - Applicants (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - 2000-2001 Harkness Fellowships - List of Suggested Projects - Comments (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Harkness Application Packs 2000-2001 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - 2000-2001 Harkness Fellowships - Turn Down Letters (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellowships - Nominators (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellowships - Nominators Declined (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - 1999 Harkness Fellows - Selection Committee Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 151)
    - 2000 Harkness Fellows - Selection Committee Meetings, 1999-2000 (Box 151)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellows - Selection Committee Meetings (Box 151)
    - 1999 Harkness Fellowships - New Zealand Marketing Letters, 1998-1999 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - 1999-2000 Harkness Fellowships - Requests for Applications, 1998 January-September (Box 152, Folder 2-10)
    - 1999 Harkness Survey (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Canadian Fellows Development (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Canadian Fellows Development - Contract Agreement (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - 2001-2002 Canadian Fellows - Steve Morgan (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - 2001-2002 Canadian Fellows - John Lavis (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - 2001 Canadian Policy Briefing Meeting - Correspondence (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - 2000-2001 Harkness Fellows - Selection Committee Meetings (Box 153)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellows - Selection Committee Meetings (Box 153)
    - 2001 Atlantic Fellows - Selection Committee Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 153)
    - 2001 Canadian Policy Briefing Meeting (Box 154, Folder 1-3)
    - Harkness Fellows Roundtable, 1999 June (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - 1999-2000 Harkness Fellows-AHSR Roundtable, 2000 June 5 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - 2000 New Zealand Harkness Marketing, 1999-2000 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - UK Harkness Fellows Symposium, Belfast, 2000 February 11 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - 1999 Newfield Harkness Fellows Seminar, 1998-1999 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - 2000-2001 Harkness Fellows - Fund Mentors (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellows - Stephen Davies, 2000-2001 (Box 155, Folder 1-2)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellows - Panos Kanavos (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellows - John Hobbs (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellows - Nicola Gray, 2001-2002 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellows - Frances Hughes (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - 1999 Harkness Fellows Final Reporting Seminar, 2000 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellows - Rae Lamb (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellows - Elizabeth Murray (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellows - Ciaran O'Neill (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - 2001 Harkness Fellows - Jane Pirkis (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - 2002 Harkness Fellows - Peter Broadhead (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - 2002 Harkness Fellows - Alan Cass (Box 157, Folder 1-2)
    - 2002 Harkness Fellows - Peter Crampton (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - 2002 Harkness Fellows - Mark Exworthy (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - 2002 Harkness Fellows - Ronald Gray (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - 2002 Harkness Fellows - Ngaire Kerse, 2002-2003 (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - 2002 Harkness Fellows - Russell Gruen, 2002-2003 (Box 158, Folder 1-2)
    - 2002 Harkness Fellows - Timothy Scott, 2002-2003 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 2002 Harkness Fellows - Nicholas Steel, 2002-2003 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 1999 Harkness Fellows - Martin N. Marshall - Final Report, 1999 August (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - 2003 Harkness Fellows - Elizabeth Ellen Roughead, 2003-2004 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Dale Brambley (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Tom Marshall (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Stepjen Dunn (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Martin Hefford (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Nicole Laurie - Senior Fellowships Advisor, 2003-2004 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Nicole Laurie - Senior Fellowships Advisor, 2003-2004 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Malcolm Battersby (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Vikki Entwistle (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Gareth Parry (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Elizabeth Davies (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - 2004-2005 New Zealand Advertising (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - 2004-2005 UK Harkness Advertising (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - 2004-2005 Harkness Conferences (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - 2004-2005 Harkness Nominations Received (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - 2004-2005 Harkness Applications Sent (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - 2004-2005 Harkness Fellowships - Orientation Seminar, 2004 September 20-23 (Box 165, Folder 1-2)
    - 1997 Harkness Fellowships Directory (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Harkness Fellows Orientation Seminar 1997-1998, 1997 September 22-25 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellows UK Selection Committee Meeting (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - 2001-2002 New Zealand Harkness Fellowships (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellows Australian Selection Committee Meeting (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellows Nominator Lists (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellows Orientation - Yankee Tickets (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Harkness Fellowships Meeting at AHRQ, 2001 October 9 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellows Individual Projects Meeting, Washington, D. C., Capital Hilton, 2001 October 12 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Harkness Canadian Policy Briefing Tour 2005, 2005 May 3-6 (Box 167, Folder 2-3)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows Orientation Seminar, 2003 September 15-18 (Box 167, Folder 4-5)
    - 1999-2000 Harkness Fellows Site Visits, 1999 October 15 (Box 168, Folder 3-4)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellows Orientation Seminar, 1998 October 19-21 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellows Orientation Seminar, 1998 October 19-21 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellows - Mid-Fellowship Policy Seminar, 1999 February 24-26 (Box 169, Folder 2-3)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Felllows Final Reporting Seminar, 1999 June 24-25 (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - 2000 Harkness Fellows - Edwin James Pearce (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - 2004-2005 Harkness Fellows Seminar - Understanding American Politics and Public Policy, 2005 January 31-February 2 (Box 170, Folder 2-4)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellows Orientation Seminar, 2001 November 8-9 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellows Orientation Seminar, 2001 November 8-9 (Box 171, Folder 1-2)
    - 2001-2002 Harkness Fellowships Washington Policy Briefing (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - 2000-2001 Harkness Fellows - Kieran Walshe, 2000-2002 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - 2000-2001 Harkness Fellows - Colin F. Tukuitonga (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellows - Mary E. Seddon (New Zealand) (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - 1998-1999 Harkness Fellows - Bridget M. Wickham (New Zealand) (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Australian "Reverse Harkness" Fellowship, 1998-2001 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - 1998-1999 Harknes Fellows - Home Country Institution Awards (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Coordinating Committee Meeting, 2000 October 13 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Gareth Parry (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Elizabeth Ellen Roughead (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Tom Marshall (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Martin Hefford (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Vikki Entwistle (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Elizabeth Davies (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Stephen Dunn (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Malcolm Battersby (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Bramley, Dale (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellows - Peter Carl Spirvulis (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - 2004-2005 Harkness Fellows - Claire Stebbing (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - 2004-2005 Harkness Fellows - Nadeem Qureshi (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - 2004-2005 Harkness Fellows - Kathryn Marie Rowan (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - 2004-2005 Harkness Fellows - Stephen Monaghan (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - 2004-2005 Harkness Fellows - Richard Scott (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Directory of Fellows 1925-1980, 1981 (Box 176)
    - Directory of Fellows and Commonwealth Fund 1925-1985, 1986 (Box 176)
    - Harkness Fellows - Database 1997 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - 1989-2002 Harkness Fellows Contact List (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Harkness Report, 1990-1996 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Harkness Fellows - Canadian Policy Briefing 2002 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Harkness Fellows - Canadian Policy Briefing 2003 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - 2003-2004 Harkness Fellowships-AHRQ Meeting, 2003 October 21 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Harkness Canadian Policy Briefing Tour 2005, 2005 May 3-6 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Canadian Health Services Research, Harkness Fellows Programme, 2004 May 4-7 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Directory of Commonwealth Fund and Harkness Fellows, 1925-1990, 1991 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - 1999 Harkness Fellows in Health Care Policy Roundtable Discussions (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Harkness Fellows Final Reporting Seminar: Robin Osborn Dinner Talking Points, 2000 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Harkness Fellows Orientation Notes, Presentations, Budgets, Agendas and Meetings, 2004-2007 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - International Health Articles, Presentations and Surveys 2002-2004, German and French Health Care System (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Robin Osborn's Notes, 2004-2005 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - 2002-2003 Harkness Fellowships in Health Care Policy - United Kingdom Selection Committee Meetings (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - 1995 Harkness Fellowships Handbook - Tab 17-21 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - 1995 Atlantic Fellowships Handbook (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Sir Jeremy Morse - Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Alfred A. Atherton (ALA) - Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 196, Folder 4-5)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Resigned Fellowships, 1969-1989 (Box 197, Folder 1-3)
      Restricted - Personnel material.
    - Sir Alan Bailey - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Rosemary Murray - Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Mary Goldring - Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Sir Edwin Nixon - Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Lord Dainton - Correspondence, 1984-1990 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Lady Albemarle - Correspondence, 1964-1989 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Robert Glaser - Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Alfred L. Atherton (ALA) - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Andrew Knight - Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Lady Warnock - Correspondence, 1983-1989 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - R. L. Ireland - Correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Harriet Belin - Correspondence, 1979-1986 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - David Hancock - Correspondence, 1984-1993 (Box 199, Folder 1-2)
    - C. Sims Farr - Correspondence, 1971-1993 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Carleton B. Chapman - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Calvin Plimpton - Correspondence, 1966-1987 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Robert Sproull - Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Faxes To/From New York, 1990-1991 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Policy - Budget Division, 1979-1991 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Policy - Budget: Fellows, 1969-1990 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - New York - Board Members, 1980-1987 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Harkness Fellows - Annual Forms, 1950-1982 (Box 201, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence - To/From New York, 1986-1989 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Committees - General, 1966-1979 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - British Selection Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - British Selection Committee, 1982-1989 (Box 202, Folder 1-4)
    - Harkness Fellowships - Journal Entries, Distributions, 1982-1983 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Harkness Fellowships - Excerpts from Minutes, Board of Directors, 1925-1974 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - London Office Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - London Statements, 1975-1982 (Box 203, Folder 2-4)
    - London Budgets, 1959-1981 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Fellowship Budgets - Other Than London, 1981-1982 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Harkness Fellowships Costs, 1980-1981 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Harkness Fellowships - Procedures (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Division of International Fellowships - Budget Sheets (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Harkness Fellowships - Cost Data (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Harkness Fellowships Distribution Journal Entries, 1973-1981 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Memorandum - Harkness Fellowships, 1978-1982 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - London Reconciliation Statement, 1981-1982 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn (990562) - Harkness Fellowships, 2000-2001, 1999-2004 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Commonwealth Fund - Osborn (970664) - Harkness Fellowships, 1997-1998 and 1998-1999, 1997-2002 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - IHP Financial Administration, 4
    - Tax Withholdings, 1987-1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - London Statements, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - London Statements, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - RFP's, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
    - Administrative Checks, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Checks, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF), 5
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1997 March 24 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1997 May 6 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1997 June 20 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1997 June 23 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1997 November 5 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1998 January 16 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1998 March 17 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1998 April 8 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1998 May 28 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1998 June 17 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1998 July 29 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1998 October 1 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1998 October 1 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1998 November 5 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Turndowns 1999, 1999-2000 (Box 51, Folder 3-6)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Turndowns 1999, 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Turndowns 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - PDF 990840 - Pharmaceuticals and the Elderly, Deborah A. Freund, 1998-2000 (Box 91, Folder 1-2)
    - PDF 990898 - Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) Health Task Force, 1999-2001 (Box 91, Folder 3-5)
    - PDF 990898 - Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) Health Task Force, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - William Plowden - Plan for Developing and Implementing the Harkness Fellows Association and Transatlantic Trust, 1998-2000 (Box 92, Folder 2-3)
    - PDF 980883 - Conference on Future of Hospital-Non Primary Care, Theodore Marmor, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - PDF 980884 - U.S.-Canada Comparative Health Care Conference, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Australian Coordinated Care Trial Representatives, New York City Meeting, 2000 June 9 (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) 1998-1999 Turndowns (Box 93, Folder 3-5)
    - Aiken (980425) - International Evaluation of Variation in Hospital Outcomes (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Contracts, 1992-1996 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2001 January 30 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2001 March 13 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2001 April 17 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2001 May 16 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2001 June 17 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2001 August 21 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2001 September 25 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2001 November 7 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2001 December 18 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) - Kay, Jennifer - Canadian Consulate, 2001 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) - Kay, Jennifer - Canadian Consulate, 2000-2001 (Box 113, Folder 1-2)
    - Ray Moynihan Dissemination Proposal, 2000 (Box 113, Folder 3-4)
    - Australian Coordinated Care Trial Representatives, New York City Meeting, 2000 June 19 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1999 January 6 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1999 February 3 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1999 March 25 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1999 April 28 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1999 May 27 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1999 June 16 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1999 August 4 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1999 November 2 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 1999 December 14 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2000 January 25 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2000 March 28 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2000 May 16 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2000 June 13 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2000 July 5 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2000 August 1 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2000 September 12 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2000 November 16 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) Meeting, 2000 December 14 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Commonwealth Fund - Quarterly, 1999 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Commonwealth Fund Board Meeting, 1999 April (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Commonwealth Fund Board Meeting, 1999 November (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Program Monitoring Committee Meeting, 1999 June 11 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - PDF - Simanski, Hannah - Israel National Institute of Health Policy (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) - Turndowns 2001 (Box 115, Folder 4-5)
    - PDF - AHSR 2002 Annual Meeting - International Panel - Pittman (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - PDF - McMaster University - John Lavis (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - PDF - International Conference US-UK, NYAM (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - PDF - International Session at 2001 Annual AHSR Meeting (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - 2001 AHSR Annual Meeting - IHP Panel (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - PDF 20010260 - University of Pennsylvania, Aiken (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - PDF - Media Toolkit for Journalist - Ray Moynihan (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Second Jerusalem International Conference on Health Policy (980944), 1998 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - IHEA - Tom Getzen (980942), 1998-1999 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Richard Coker (980672), 1998 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - U. S. Health Policy - Development of Background Reading List, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Review of Currently Funded Projects for Harkness Fellows (980747), 1998 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - 1998 Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - U. S. - Canada Comparative Health Care Conference, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 2-3)
    - Reconsidering the Role of Competition in Health Care Markets - UCLA - Brown, 1999-2000 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - AHSR - Cross National Health Services and Policy Research (990421), 1999 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Yale University - Four Country Conference (Canada, Germany, United States, Netherlands), 1998-1999 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - President's Discretionary Fund (PDF) - Turndowns 2001 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Symposiums and Surveys, 6
    - 1999 International Symposium - Seven Country Long-Term Care, 1999 August (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - 1999 International Symposium - Seven Country Long-Term Care, 1999 August (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Blair House Dinner, 1998 October (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Keynote Speaker - Hillary Rodham Clinton, 1998 October (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - General Correspondence, 1998 October (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Secretary Shalala Correspondence, 1998 October (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Ministers of Health Correspondence, 1998 October (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Authors - Jane Hall, 1998 October (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Authors - Uwe E. Reinhardt, 1998 October (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Authors - Reviewer Comments, 1998 October (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Authors - Karen D. Poutasi, 1998 October (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Authors - C. David Naylor, 1998 October (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Authors - Julian Le Grand, 1998 October (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Authors - Correspondence, 1998 October (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - 1998 International Symposium on Health Care Policy - Invitation Letters, 1998 October (Box 54, Folder 7)